Guide to the Stanford University, Center for East Asian Studies, Student Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Center for East Asian Studies, student records
1965-2007
SC0982
Stanford University. Center for East Asian Studies.
10 Linear feet
Files on students earning degrees in East Asian Studies.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
Access: Only student papers within the files are accessible for research use; please consult with the University Archivist for access. No photocopying of student papers is permitted.
Description of the Collection
Files on students earning degrees in East Asian Studies.
Access Terms
Stanford University. Center for East Asian Studies.; Student papers.
Collection Contents
- Records, Accession ARCH-2010-032
  Only student papers within the files are accessible for research use.
  - Baker, George A., MA(1967), 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Cole, James H. MA (1969), 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Barab, Peter G. MA (1972), 1968-1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Fitts Jr., Charles E. MA (1975), 1968-1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Gruer, Kathleen A. MA (1970), 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Hamant, Susan MA (1970), 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Rapp, William V. MA (1970), 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Richter, Jeanne MA (1970), 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Young, Susan E. MA (1969), 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Harwell, Henry O. MA (1971), 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Ipson, Michael K. MA (1973), 1969-1973 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Joseph, William A. MA (1971), 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Kearns, Rosemary MA (1971), 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - McCorkle, Malcolm MA (1971), 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - McFarland, Lynn B. MA (1971), 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Phillips, Robert A. MA (1970), 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Hitt, Alan B. MA (1971), 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Kelley, David E. MA (1972), 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Lautz, Terrill E. MA (1972), 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Lawrence, Hugh MA (1973), 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Lipman, Jonathan N. MA (1974), 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Martin, Earl S. MA (1972), 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Nakagawa, Lillian K. MA (1972), 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Osterweis, Suno K. MA (1972), 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Piggott, Joan R. MA (1972), 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Shepherd, John R. MA (1973), 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Thomas, Stephen C. MA (1972), 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Broderick, Lorraine MA (1972), 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Chizeck, Susan P. MA (1972), 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Cogley, William L. MA (1972), 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Cory Jr., Gerald A. MA (1972), 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Coye, Joel C. MA (1972), 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Delphs Jr., Robert A. MA (1973), 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Fuertado, Gardel M. MA (1972), 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Gadsen, James I. MA (1972), 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Gardner, John D. MA (1972), 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Andreasen, Andrew J. MA (1973), 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Chauncey, Helen R. MA (1973), 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Coleman, Maryruth MA (1973), 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Doner, Richard F. MA (1973), 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Entenmann, Robert E. MA (1973), 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Holland, John G., 1971 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Lee, Nim-Yee H. MA (1973), 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Turner, Christena L. MA (1975), 1971-1975 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Welch, Judith A. MA (1974), 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Chinwanno, Chulacheeb MA (1974), 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Chu, Susette H.H. MA (1975), 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - David, Steven R. MA (1975), 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Edwards, James W. MA (1975), 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Gische, David M. MA (1975), 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Harding, Roca L. MA (1973), 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Higham, Indira V. MA (1975), 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Obenchain, Diane B. MA (1974), 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Pessin, John MA (1974), 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Siu, Helen F. MA (1974), 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Tom, Eugene MA (1974), 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Arnold, Walter, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Bestor, Theodore C., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Burch, Benjamin MA (1975), 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Goggin, Malcolm L., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Jones, Phillip A. MA (1974), 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Keller, Helen E. MA (1975), 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Sterling, Bess L. MA (1975), 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Wong, Sandra M. J. MA (1975), 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Abdul, Rahman din H.I., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Bergenstein, Sigrid MA (1976), 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Creagan, John P., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Eisinger, Joel MA (1975), 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Heftel, Christopher L., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - King, Kenton J., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Koblitz, Donald J. MA (1975), 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Mesina, Charmaine F., 1974 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Meyer, Ted R. MA (1976), 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - O'Neil, John J., 1974 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Reilly, James V. MA (1976), 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Ross, Clarence T., 1974 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Takemoto, Akira R. MA (1976), 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Tarui, Sumio, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Terry, Edith B. MA (1976), 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Winter, Prescott B. MA (1976), 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Honig, Emily MA (1977), 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Mower, Garth C. BA (1979), 1975-1979 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Nao, Yasue R., 1975 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Nomoto, Yoshio MA (1976), 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Sandberg, Kay H. MA (1977), 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Thompson, Michael G. MA (1977), 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Chin, Mary Y., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Crook, Carl M., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Gleit, David H., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Mosher, Steven W. MA (1977), 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Myers, Steven W., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Rofel, Lisa B., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Rosner, Marni H., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Sasaki, Yuri MA (1977), 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Suzuki, Anne H. MA (1977), 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Brolley, William (Wolfgang) BA (1981), 1977-1981 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Chester, Richard S., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Chuang, Miao-Huei, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Gree, Danielle J., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Horowitz, Stephen D., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Huey, Robert N., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Jones, Russell B., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Lim, Chun W., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Low, Linda W., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Miller, Bernard S., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Moonshine, Leslie, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Myers, Nancy E., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Nichols, Elizabeth, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Oyama, Lisa S., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Robins, Lisa D., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Sachs, David E., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Yorke, Karen M., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Elms, Teresa BA (1978) (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Fickle, Floyd BA (1978) (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Sturman, Peter C. BA (1978) (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Wu, Robin BA (1978) (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Chen, Chiu-Kun, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Diamond, Deborah C. MA (1980), 19781980 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Fridley, David, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Gilbert, Wendy L., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Ishibashi, Chiyoko, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Reynolds, Jonathan, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Saltzman, Katherine P., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Smith, Audra B., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Wallace, John, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Ardourel, Jill R., 1979 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Cheng, Mark D., 1979 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Golding, Sabina, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Kato, Louise C., 1979 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Pickerell, Blair, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Price, Betty J., 1979 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Ribeiro, Jorge F., 1979 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Shenitz, Bruce, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Thomas, Martha C., 1979 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Villanueva, Marianne, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Robertson, Thomas Lee BA (1980) (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Chang, Michael S.H. MA (1981), 19801981 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Corrigan, Robert MA (1982), 19801982 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Deming, Rust, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Faison, Barbara, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Finlayson, Grant, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - Graven, Kathryn, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - Heaton, Jenine L. MA (1981), 19801981 (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - Huston, David H., 1980 (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - Kaya, Karen T. MA (1981), 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 145)
  - Lee, Lillian L., 1980 (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - Revoir, Richard C., 1980 (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - Sadoshima, Shiro, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 148)
  - Sakaue, Marlene J., 1980 (Box 3, Folder 149)
  - Storm, Mary N.G. MA (1986), 1980-1986 (Box 3, Folder 150)
  - Takeuchi, Toshitaka, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - Wallace, Wendy, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 152)
  - Attwood, Polly BA (1981) (Box 3, Folder 153)
  - Hale, Ellen D. BA (1981) (Box 3, Folder 154)
  - Lee, Cynthia A. BA (1981) (Box 3, Folder 155)
  - Reese, Marsha BA (1981) (Box 3, Folder 156)
  - Russell, Rebecca BA (1981) (Box 3, Folder 157)
  - Wolfe, Constance BA (1981) (Box 3, Folder 158)
  - Algarin, Joanne P., 1981 (Box 3, Folder 159)
  - Biell, Ronald L., 1981 (Box 3, Folder 160)
  - Donahey, Helen L.G., 1981 (Box 3, Folder 161)
  - James, John G., 1981 (Box 3, Folder 162)
  - Keirstead, Thomas MA (1983), 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - Miller, Lee K., 1981 (Box 3, Folder 164)
  - Munekata, Shizu, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - Oshima, Eiichi, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 166)
  - Rickansrud, Melony, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 167)
  - Sarnoff, Linda A., 1981 (Box 4, Folder 168)
  - Shapiro, Hugh MA (1983), 19811983 (Box 4, Folder 169)
  - Liu, Michael E. BA (1982) (Box 4, Folder 170)
  - Mathre, Eric BA (1982) (Box 4, Folder 171)
  - Shapiro, Hugh L. BA (1982) (Box 4, Folder 172)
  - Akagawa, Roy K., 1982 (Box 4, Folder 173)
  - Atkins, William, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 174)
  - Babb, James D., 1982 (Box 4, Folder 175)
  - Hultgren, Linda F., 1982 (Box 4, Folder 176)
  - Lewis, Charles Bernard MA (1984), 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 177)
  - Onan, Jill M., 1982 (Box 4, Folder 178)
  - Peyran, Nicoletta, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 179)
  - Poskanzer, Deborah R., 1982 (Box 4, Folder 180)
  - Sato, Nancy, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 181)
  - Staenberg, Jonathan, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 182)
  - Wong, Lydia A., 1982 (Box 4, Folder 183)
  - Black, Kelly H. BA (1983) (Box 4, Folder 184)
  - Sakurako, Daniel BA (1983) (Box 4, Folder 185)
  - Benedict, Carol A. MA (1984), 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 186)
  - Bergman, Charles K. MA (1984), 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 187)
  - Bohlen, Nina MA (1985), 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 188)
  - Eisenberg, Andrew MA (1984), 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 189)
  - Gregory, Juliette MA (1985), 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 190)
  - Levy, Robert J., 1983 (Box 4, Folder 191)
  - Riddle, Robin, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 192)
  - Rogers, John D., 1983 (Box 4, Folder 193)
  - Rose, Leslie M., 1983 (Box 4, Folder 194)
  - Zeichner, Lee M. MA (1984), 19831984 (Box 4, Folder 195)
  - Geyling, Andrea I. BA (1984) (Box 4, Folder 196)
  - Tom, Naomi Carol BA (1984) (Box 4, Folder 197)
  - Yang, Phillip MA (1984) (Box 5, Folder 198)
  - Bettinger, Paul MA (1986), 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 199)
  - Duxbury, Pauline E.C., 1984 (Box 5, Folder 200)
  - Erickson, Britta L., 1984 (Box 5, Folder 201)
  - Fujii, Shari, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 202)
  - Gamberton, Margaret, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 203)
  - Helsell, Kristina M. MA (1986), 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 204)
  - Kafalas, Phillip A. MA (1985), 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 205)
  - Koehler, Kyle E. MA (1986), 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 206)
  - Lee, Tahirih, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 207)
  - Rasmussen, Samuel G., 1984 (Box 5, Folder 208)
  - Shaw, Bing, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 209)
  - Tokuchi, Tatsuhito, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 210)
  - Townsend, Deborah E., 1984 (Box 5, Folder 211)
  - Whitney, Stephen H., 1984 (Box 5, Folder 212)
  - Cucek, Michael BA (1985) (Box 5, Folder 213)
  - Fujii, Naoko BA (1985) (Box 5, Folder 214)
  - Mass, Karen S. BA (1985) (Box 5, Folder 215)
  - Reith, Tracy BA (1985) (Box 5, Folder 216)
  - Chin, Arthur MA (1986), 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 217)
  - Desmond, Elizabeth A. MA (1986), 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 218)
  - Donahoe, Eileen E., 1985 (Box 5, Folder 219)
  - Donenfeld, June, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 220)
  - Klebes, Daniel H. MA (1986), 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 221)
  - Mak, Terence W., 1985 (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - Kim, Carrie E. BA (1986) (Box 6, Folder 223)
  - Ward, Eric J. BA (1986) (Box 6, Folder 224)
  - Yamamura, Jon BA (1986) (Box 6, Folder 225)
  - Adler, Michael J., 1986 (Box 6, Folder 226)
  - Bakalar, Steven D., 1986 (Box 6, Folder 227)
  - Godfrey, John M., 1986 (Box 6, Folder 228)
  - Gorell, Kristin A., 1986 (Box 6, Folder 229)
  - Guilhamet, Roxanne, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 230)
  - Inui, Margaret, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 231)
  - Kuo, Mark D., 1986 (Box 6, Folder 232)
  - Lance, Gregory C., 1986 (Box 6, Folder 233)
  - Matsubara, Kerne, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 234)
  - Murdo, Patricia, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 235)
  - Slocum, Susan, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 236)
  - Strate, Helen B., 1986 (Box 6, Folder 237)
  - Suto, Noriko, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 238)
  - Banner, Lawrence D. BA (1987) (Box 6, Folder 239)
  - Adams, Christopher E. MA (1990), 1987-1990 (Box 6, Folder 240)
  - Barker, Conan, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 241)
  - Brown, Steven, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 242)
  - Chiu, Wendy, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 243)
  - Ji, Jing-Er, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 244)
  - Miller, Elizabeth K. MA (1989), 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 245)
  - Noonan, Joyce K., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 246)
  - Perry, Julia T., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 247)
  - Robinson, Kenneth R., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 248)
  - Trumbull, Joanna H. MA (1989), 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 249)
  - Tsoi, Julie Michelle, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 250)
  - Bui, Marguerite L. BA (1988) (Box 7, Folder 251)
  - Moos, Ryan R. BA (1988) (Box 7, Folder 252)
  - Nagy, Catherine BA (1988) (Box 7, Folder 253)
  - Peters, Emily BA (1988) (Box 7, Folder 254)
  - Anuzis, Adria M., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 255)
  - Bernell, Robert W., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 256)
  - Bertolino, Gina M. MA (1990), 1988-1990 (Box 7, Folder 257)
  - Chapin, John M., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 258)
  - Crocken, Laura J., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 259)
  - Efron, Ellen J. MA (1990), 19881990 (Box 7, Folder 260)
  - Gallavan, Timothy MA (1990), 1988-1990 (Box 7, Folder 261)
  - Hunter-Chester, David, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 262)
  - Jeevanjee, Salma A. MA (1991), 19881991 (Box 7, Folder 263)
  - Kieffer, Anthony R., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 264)
  - Klein, Wendy, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 265)
  - Laschever, Adam R., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 266)
  - Ortiz, Jamie L., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 267)
  - Pixley, Thomas H., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 268)
  - Shein, Jean-Emmanuel MA (1990), 19881990 (Box 7, Folder 269)
  - Takata, Azumi, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 270)
  - Tatman, Julia L., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 271)
  - Chapin, John M. BA (1989) (Box 7, Folder 272)
  - Hendricks, Elizabeth G. BA (1989) (Box 7, Folder 273)
  - Huang, Valerie H. BA&MA(1989 BA) (Box 7, Folder 274)
  - Lee, Joyce T. BA (1989) (Box 7, Folder 275)
  - Mahon, John P. BA (1989) (Box 8, Folder 276)
  - Ruskola, Teemu BA (1989) (Box 8, Folder 277)
  - Abrahamson, Debbie L. MA (1991), 19891991 (Box 8, Folder 278)
  - Bomar, Kimberly A., 1989 (Box 8, Folder 279)
  - Bryan, Steven L., 1989 (Box 8, Folder 280)
  - Cernosia, Christine E. MA (1991), 19891991 (Box 8, Folder 281)
  - Fiore, Rozanna L., 1989 (Box 8, Folder 282)
  - Garvey, Michael, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 283)
  - Han, Chang H., 1989 (Box 8, Folder 284)
  - Henderson, Elizabeth C., 1989 (Box 8, Folder 285)
  - Huo, Ricky, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 286)
  - Ishikawa, Hiroshi, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 287)
  - Katae, Takashi, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 288)
  - King, Kristin, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 289)
  - Kiyasu, Crawford M.P. MA (1991), 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 290)
  - Moriyama, Susan M. MA (1991), 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 291)
  - Saidel, Andrew M., 1989 (Box 8, Folder 292)
  - Searight, Amy E., 1989 (Box 8, Folder 293)
  - Sulkin, Seth R., 1989 (Box 8, Folder 294)
  - Wilson, Eric G., 1989 (Box 8, Folder 295)
  - Winden, Andrew W., 1989 (Box 8, Folder 296)
  - Chen, Connie BA (1990) (Box 8, Folder 297)
  - Chen, Sabina BA (1990) (Box 8, Folder 298)
  - Garlinghouse, Mark BA (1990) (Box 8, Folder 299)
  - Gilbert, Jay BA (1990) (Box 8, Folder 300)
  - Heginbotham, Arlen BA (1990) (Box 9, Folder 301)
  - Klapper, Dana BA (1990) (Box 9, Folder 302)
  - Mak, Suzanna BA (1990) (Box 9, Folder 303)
  - Rosen, Erin Jennifer BA (1990) (Box 9, Folder 304)
  - Ruhl, Suzanne BA (1990) (Box 9, Folder 305)
  - Watanabe, Kim BA (1990) (Box 9, Folder 306)
  - Wood, Nora BA (1990) (Box 9, Folder 307)
  - Bartels, Matthew G., 1990 (Box 9, Folder 308)
  - Berkson, Mark A., 1990 (Box 9, Folder 309)
  - Blumental, David M., 1990 (Box 9, Folder 310)
  - Bosak, Michael, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 311)
  - Casman, Jesse S., 1990 (Box 9, Folder 312)
  - Chuang, Sherry L., 1990 (Box 9, Folder 313)
  - DeSombre, Michael, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 314)
  - Ishizuka, Hideki, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 315)
  - Kraft, Natalie R., 1990 (Box 9, Folder 316)
  - Krisher, Deborah, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 317)
  - Lee, Lisa M. MA (1992), 19901992 (Box 9, Folder 318)
  - Li, Jing, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 319)
  - Mahony, Tarrant M., 1990 (Box 9, Folder 320)
  - Matsuo, Kaoru MA (1991), 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 321)
  - Pang, Janice M., 1990 (Box 9, Folder 322)
  - Pinneo, Thomas M., 1990 (Box 9, Folder 323)
  - Rosenfeld, David M., 1990 (Box 9, Folder 324)
  - Ryan, Sharon, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 325)
  - Wood, John C., 1990 (Box 9, Folder 326)
  - Handley, J.B. BA (1991) (Box 9, Folder 327)
  - Jorgensen, Mary Anne BA (1991) (Box 9, Folder 328)
  - Lambird, Elizabeth BA (1991) (Box 9, Folder 329)
  - Lee, Alice BA (1991) (Box 10, Folder 330)
  - Strauss, Adam BA (1991) (Box 10, Folder 331)
  - Clayton, Cathryn H., 1991 (Box 10, Folder 332)
  - Epstein, Shari, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 333)
  - Fernsebner, Susan R., 1991 (Box 10, Folder 334)
  - Fincher, Leta H. MA (1993), 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 335)
  - Findlay, Beverly L., 1991 (Box 10, Folder 336)
  - Fritz, Jonathan D. MA (1992), 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 337)
  - Huang, Benjamin MA (1993), 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 338)
  - Jen, Andrew W. MA (1993), 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 339)
  - Leicester, Elizabeth A., 1991 (Box 10, Folder 340)
  - Meyers, Christian W. MA (1993), 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 341)
  - Nishida, Takahiro, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 342)
  - Schreib, Claudia A., 1991 (Box 10, Folder 343)
  - Trager, Glenn A. MA (1993), 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 344)
  - Wice, Leila R., 1991 (Box 10, Folder 345)
  - Widenhoefer, James F., 1991 (Box 10, Folder 346)
  - Benvenuto, Kecia BA (1992) (Box 10, Folder 347)
  - Kim, Kevin D. BA (1992) (Box 10, Folder 348)
  - Kleinhoff, Keleigh BA (1992) (Box 10, Folder 349)
  - Okimoto, Jolyn K. BA (1992) (Box 10, Folder 350)
  - Sano, Cheryl A. BA (1992) (Box 10, Folder 351)
  - Butler, Donald G., 1992 (Box 10, Folder 352)
  - Chu, Richard T. MA (1994), 1992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 353)
  - Chubb, Oliver MA (1994), 19921994 (Box 10, Folder 354)
  - Dole, Gwendolyn F. MA (1993), 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 355)
  - Figueroa, Rowena, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 356)
  - Filliol, Oliver, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 357)
  - Girouard, Mark J., 1992 (Box 11, Folder 358)
  - Hurley, Robert R., 1992 (Box 11, Folder 359)
  - Ikeda, Carol H. MA (1994), 19921994 (Box 11, Folder 360)
  - Irminger, Betticlare, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 361)
  - Leno, Jacqueline K., 1992 (Box 11, Folder 362)
  - Li, Linda C., 1992 (Box 11, Folder 363)
  - Liu, Tiffany N., 1992 (Box 11, Folder 364)
  - Pomfret, John, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 365)
  - Rodriguez, Natalie, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 366)
  - Saxon, Antonia B., 1992 (Box 11, Folder 367)
  - Seaman, Thomas J. MA (1994), 19921994 (Box 11, Folder 368)
  - Wilkey, Andrew. MA (1994), 1992-1994 (Box 11, Folder 369)
  - Berman, Marc BA (1993) (Box 11, Folder 370)
  - Chu, Li Shi MA (1995), 19931995 (Box 11, Folder 371)
  - Drake, Joanna G. MA (1995), 1993-1995 (Box 11, Folder 372)
  - Furigay, Tara A., 1993 (Box 11, Folder 373)
  - Herlihy, Martin C., 1993 (Box 11, Folder 374)
  - Hotta, Tomoko MA (1995), 1993-1995 (Box 11, Folder 375)
  - Katsunuma, Mari, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 376)
  - Koppe, Laurence R., 1993 (Box 12, Folder 377)
  - Lee, Alice N. MA (1995), 19931995 (Box 12, Folder 378)
  - Maley, Matthew, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 379)
  - Mehta, Sujeet D., 1993 (Box 12, Folder 380)
  - Moore, Carey Lynn, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 381)
  - Mori, Brent D., 1993 (Box 12, Folder 382)
  - Nogaki, Jenifer Y. MA (1995), 1993-1995 (Box 12, Folder 383)
  - Park, Jae Sun Mary, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 384)
  - Patent, Jason D., 1993 (Box 12, Folder 385)
  - Plum, M. Colette, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 386)
  - Sehestedt, Melissa A., 1993 (Box 12, Folder 387)
  - Stalker, Nancy K., 1993 (Box 12, Folder 388)
  - Stark, Glenn A. MA (1995), 19931995 (Box 12, Folder 389)
  - Stein, Matthew J. MA (1995), 1993-1995 (Box 12, Folder 390)
  - Suttmeier, Bruce R., 1993 (Box 12, Folder 391)
  - Tang, William W., 1993 (Box 12, Folder 392)
  - Benskin, Elizabeth MA (1996), 19941996 (Box 12, Folder 393)
  - Bien, William J., 1994 (Box 12, Folder 394)
  - Blackford, Randall F. MA (1996), 1994-1996 (Box 12, Folder 395)
  - Bolin, Nathaniel, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 396)
  - Bonder, Cherie L. MA (1995), 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 397)
  - Chan, Jayston S. MA (1998), 1994-1998 (Box 12, Folder 398)
  - Christ, Julie MA (1996), 19941996 (Box 12, Folder 399)
  - Chu, Pei Hwa, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 400)
  - Deming, Jennifer MA (1995), 19941995 (Box 13, Folder 401)
  - Dennis III, George E. MA (1995), 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 402)
  - Fine, Gary S. MA (1995), 19941995 (Box 13, Folder 403)
  - Gilbert, Clark G. MA (1995), 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 404)
  - Hsieh, Lilli MA (1995), 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 405)
  - McReynolds, Becky S. MA (1996), 1994-1996 (Box 13, Folder 406)
  - Mitsui, Hideko MA (1997), 1994-1997 (Box 13, Folder 407)
  - Rubin, Adam W. MA (1995), 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 408)
  - Schiaffini Vedani, Patricia I. MA (1995), 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 409)
  - Tomsen, Kim-Anh MA (1996), 1994-1996 (Box 13, Folder 410)
  - Torii, Daishi, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 411)
  - Tsai, Suefen K., 1994 (Box 13, Folder 412)
  - Wang, Edward C.L., 1994 (Box 13, Folder 413)
  - Won, Julie A. MA (1997), 1994-1997 (Box 13, Folder 414)
  - Young, Jocelyn S. MA (1996), 1994-1996 (Box 13, Folder 415)
  - Yum, Steve, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 416)
  - Kojima, Hugh BA (1995) (Box 13, Folder 417)
  - Lasker, Johanna BA (1995) (Box 14, Folder 418)
  - Spicer, James BA (1995) (Box 14, Folder 419)
  - Cheng, Amy J. H. MA (1998), 1995-1998 (Box 14, Folder 420)
  - Curtis, Ken R. MA (1996), 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 421)
  - Harrington, Brendan L., 1995 (Box 14, Folder 422)
  - Hwang, Kenneth J., 1995 (Box 14, Folder 423)
  - Jen, Edward Y. MA (1997), 1995-1997 (Box 14, Folder 424)
  - Johnston, Alexandra MA (1996), 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 425)
  - Kwong, Bill MA (1995), 19951995 (Box 14, Folder 426)
  - Lee, Christy H. MA (1997), 1995-1997 (Box 14, Folder 427)
  - Liauw, Julita M., 1995 (Box 14, Folder 428)
  - McCaw, Becky J. MA (1996), 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 429)
  - Pearlman, Charles, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 430)
  - Ron, Roy, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 431)